<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="Black Forrest" Logo="https://imgur.com/a/ARIngYT" Description="The old world is gone.">
		<Server Name="Black Forrest" Logo="https://imgur.com/a/ARIngYT">
			<Description>
Afterlife is designed to be an immersive, hardcore, survival overhaul that works with and supports cooperative multiplayer.

Here's a (non-comprehensive) list of some of the mod's features:
- Full "action skill" system. All attributes and skills are action skills. There are no traditional levels.
- All perks are new/custom.
- No time, compass, or map to start with. These items must be acquired.
- No traders or quests (for now; an alternative is being worked on).
- Vitality system. A "general well-being" resource that can be managed in many ways.
- Reworked biomes (forest and desert in particular).
- Reworked world lighting.
- Wasteland megacity (make sure you use RWG with the mod running).
- Several classes and class selection on game start.
- Custom equipment slots including torch, backpack, watch, map, and compass.
- 3 new tool/weapon tiers including scrap, bronze, and inconel.
- Izayo's weapon packs, so lots and lots of guns (fully integrated with progression).
- UI rework.
- 6 new "mineables".
- Forge heat system.
- Permanent infection (don't worry, it's manageable).
- Quantity/liquid storage system using glass jars as main item container.
- Weight + backpack capacity inventory system.
- "Dye Tub" enabling crafting of 512 different dye colours.
- "Cartography Table" for sharing map information with allies.
- "Training Dummy" for when you're too scared to go out at night.
- Improved rain effects.
- Some optimisations to try and squeeze a bit more FPS out of the game.
- Blueprint-based building system.
- Various QoL hotkeys (can be seen in-game in the vanilla "info panel").
- And lots of other stuff!

Please see the in-game credits to see what modders and artists made this mod possible.
			</Description>
			<Author>redbeardt</Author>
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<Discord>https://discord.gg/2cfHGJQhBR</Discord>
			<Donate>https://ko-fi.com/redbeardt</Donate>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/ToBeauty/Black-Forrest-V1</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>
